http://www.mensor.com/privacypolicy_en_um.WIKA

Our website uses cookies. By continuing to use it, you agree to their use.
Further information
Agree
Are you right here?
We offer a local website for ###country###.
Change now
Stay here
Are you right here?
For ###country###, we recommend our corporate website.
Working with MensorJob OpportunitiesCareer
Sales & Service ContactsRequest a QuoteContact Us FormChat with usCustomer Feedback FormSocial MediaEmail Sign-UpMap to MensorWIKA WorldwideContact
Products
AutomotiveAvionics / AerospaceHVACManufacturingMedical / PharmaceuticalMilitaryPower EngineeringOil and GasSemiconductorResearch & EducationCalibration ServicesOEMIndustries
Calibration Service and RepairExpedited CalibrationContact ServiceDownload SoftwareService
Datasheets
Pressure
Temperature
Current, Voltage, Resistance
Digital Barometers
Air Data
Custom Instruments
Operating instructions
Privacy Policy
In general, Mensor LP (hereinafter referred to as "Mensor" or "we") acts according to data avoidance and minimization principles. This means we try to collect, process and use as little personal information as possible.
So that you can feel secure with respect to the handling of your personal data, we make it transparent what happens to the accumulated data and what security measures are taken on our part. We will also let you know what your legal rights are in connection with the treatment of this data.1. Automatically generated dataOur website can generally be visited without entering any personal data. We just collect the data supplied by your internet service provider. This includes the name of your provider, your IP address, the type of browser you use and your operating system as well as visited websites including any search terms and the websites from which you visit our website. In these cases, data is processed anonymously, which makes it impossible for us to relate the data to your person (= identification). An evaluation is only carried out for statistical purposes. The personal data you provide is generally used only within Mensor.2. Personal data and consentInsofar as it is required for the establishment, execution or termination of a contractual relationship or quasi agreement with customers, we will collect, process and use your personal data. Furthermore, we will only save personal data if the website visitor enters it explicitly and voluntarily. This might be the case, for example, if a website visitor wants to register for certain parts of the website. The information submitted in this case will only be used according to its purpose and observing the valid legal requirements; any use beyond the above mentioned requires your consent. A consent may be revoked any time in writing by sending the request to our data protection contact.Your contact person for data protection issues at Mensor is:
Name:
Larry Mock
E-mail:
Marketing@mensor.com
Postal address:
Mensor201 Barnes Dr.San Marcos, TX 78666
3. Forwarding personal dataData are generally collected, processed and used by us only. In certain cases, however, your data is also collected, processed and used by other companies of the WIKA Group (affiliate companies) or by service providers having a business relationship with us. In the last-mentioned cases, however, we will see to it that the relevant legal data protection requirements and the obligations resulting from this data protection notice will be complied with. Any further access to your information by third parties is not intended by us. In particular, we will not sell your information or use it in any similar way. We will comply with our duty of notification as required by law or authorities; in these cases, we will forward the relevant information to the public authorities.4. Security principlesTo protect the information about employees/customers/suppliers stored in our company against accidental or deliberate manipulations, loss, destruction or access by unauthorized parties, we have taken the corresponding technical and organizational measures. The security level is constantly being checked in cooperation with security experts and adapted to new security standards.5. NewsletterIf you have subscribed to the Mensor newsletter, you may easily unsubscribe any time. To do so,there is an unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email. After clicking the "Unsubscribe" button, you are removed from any further emails.6. Links to other websitesOur website also includes - clearly marked - links to the websites of other companies. Because these are links to independently owned websites, the contents of such websites are not under our control. Therefore, we shall not be responsible or liable for any of the contents. The providers or owners of the linked-to websites are solely liable for the contents. The linked-to pages were checked for any possible infringements or noticeable violations of the law at the moment of establishing the link. There was not any noticeable illegal contents at the moment of linking. A continuous control of the contents of the linked-to websites, however, is not reasonable without any specific evidence of a violation of the law. As soon as such violations of the law become evident, we will remove such links promptly.7. Right to information and deletionBy request, Mensor will inform you as soon as possible in writing which information that can be related to you is saved in our company. Nevertheless, if we have saved incorrect information in spite of a careful handling of your data, we will correct this information by your request. Your data is also deleted by request. Please do not hesitate to contact the data protection contact for any inquiry or request. This person is also available to you for any further questions regarding the processing of your personal data or if you have any comments or complaints that help us to further improve our data protection.
Your contact person for data protection issues at Mensor is:
Name:
Larry Mock
E-mail:
Marketing@mensor.com
Postal address:
Mensor201 Barnes Dr.San Marcos, TX 78666
8. CookiesOur websites utilizes cookies in several places. They serve to make our service more user-friendly, effective and safe. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser (locally on your hard drive). Cookies allow us to analyze how our website is used. Thus we are able to tailor the content of the site to the requirements of the user. Cookies also make it possible to measure the effectiveness of a particular advertisement and show us where best to place it depending, for example, on the topics the user is interested in. Most of the cookies we use are "session cookies". These are automatically deleted after your visit. Most web browsers accept cookies automatically. However, if you would prefer not to send this information you can usually change the settings on your browser. You will still be able to use our website without limitation (except in the case of configurators).
Last update August 17, 2016
Legal Disclosures & Disclaimers
Privacy Policy
Job opportunities
FAQ
Unit Converter
WIKA newsletter
Get the latest information and news from WIKA.
ContactMensor LP201 Barnes Drive
San Marcos, TX 78666 - USATel.: 800-984-4200E-mail: sales@mensor.com
© 2020 Mensor LP
